A loss today could have meant, quite possibly, the end of everything.
Including the Copa del rey.
Brilliant from Sergio Roberto in midfield.
A rapid counter-attack here, this looks dangerous.
Five against three on the left-hand side.
It’s a chance for Luis Suárez.
Or it’s Gomes, Gomes with the ball.
A pass, and it’s a shot!
Oh my word, what a moment!
With Messi on the pitch, there’s no need to worry, no need at all, Messi’s got this!
The all-time top scorer in the history of El Classico!
He takes it all, even in the toughest of stadiums.
Right here, at the Bernabeu .
His favourite stadium, oh Lionel!
From Rosario, what a player!
What a move from Sergio Roberto!
The hero of the comeback, he’s been involved in everything today.
A brilliant pass from Jordi Alba  to Lionel Messi.
That’s his spot.
And there’s the final whistle!
Confirming the win for Barcelona.
Their dreams of winning the La Liga is still alive!